Guide to the Cornell University College of Engineering Dean's Office records, [ca. 1916-2000]
Cornell University College of Engineering Dean's Office records, [ca. 1916-2000]
- Engineering College Council Meeting, April 10-11, 1987 (Box 113, Folder 9)
- Engineering College Council Meeting, October 2-3, 1987 (Box 113, Folder 10)
- Engineering College Council Meeting, April 22-23, 1988 (Box 113, Folder 11)
- Engineering College Council Meeting, April 10-11, 2002 (Box 114, Folder 5)